Guide to the Howard Zinn Papers TAM.542
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series X: Audio-Visual Material, 1957-2009; 448922
  This large series spans 11 linear feet, housing 466 individual items – VHS tapes, DVDs, audio recordings (reel-to-reel, cassette and CD), as well as a few older formats which cover more than fifty years of Howard Zinn's teaching, activism and public appearances. Class lectures and discussions are common as well as appearances by Zinn on radio programs as an interviewee, guest speaker or lecturer. The VHS tapes and DVDs also include performances of Zinn's plays and readings as well as a rough cut of You Can't be Neutral on a Moving Train.
  In addition to Zinn, other notable individuals such as Alice Walker, Noam Chomsky, Arundhati Roy, Eqbal Ahmad and Studs Terkel also appear.
  - Subseries X:A: Audio Cassettes, 1968-2009; 448923
    - Howard Zinn and Daniel Berrigan: Lecture on Hanoi Trip, Vietnam Committee for the Defense of Human Rights (Boston University, MA), 1968; cuid17104; 448924 (Box 86, Cd 1, Box 74, Cassette 1)
      In a small portion of this recording, a POW speaks about his cell mate, John McCain.
    - Howard Zinn: Unidentified Class Discussion, [1970]; cuid17105; 448925 (Box 74, Cassette 2)
    - Howard Zinn and William F. Buckley: Reform or Revolution (Tufts University, Medford, MA) Part 1, Jan 11, 1971; cuid17106; 448926 (Box 74, Cassette 3)
    - Howard Zinn and William F. Buckley: Reform or Revolution (Tufts University, Medford, MA) Part 2, Jan 11, 1971; cuid17107; 448927 (Box 74, Cassette 4)
    - Howard Zinn and William F. Buckley: Reform or Revolution (Tufts University, Medford, MA) Part 3 / Howard Zinn: Speech (Boston Common, MA), Jan 11, 1971 / May 5, 1971; cuid17108; 448928 (Box 74, Cassette 5)
    - Children's Music / Unidentified Class Discussion [University of Paris, Vincennes], May 16, 1974 / undated; cuid17109; 448929 (Box 74, Cassette 6)
    - Herbert Marcuse: Interviewed by Bill Moyers / John Dos Passos, The Body of an American, 1974; cuid17110; 448930 (Box 74, Cassette 7)
    - Music and Sound Effects Emma (New York, NY), 1975; cuid17111; 448931 (Box 74, Cassette 8)
    - Music / Howard Zinn: Class Discussion on Women, Oct 28, 1976; cuid17112; 448932 (Box 74, Cassette 9)
    - Howard Zinn: Class Discussion, Regulating the Poor, Challenging Information, Fall 1976; cuid17113; 448933 (Box 74, Cassette 10)
    - Howard Zinn: Discussion of the Film Salt of the Earth in "Law and Justice" Class / John Prine, "Your Flag Decal Won't Get You into Heaven Anymore", 1976, undated; cuid17114; 448934 (Box 74, Cassette 11)
    - Howard Zinn: the FBI and the RCMP (Radio Canada/CBC Presént Nationale, French Language), Jan 12, 1977; cuid17115; 448936 (Box 74, Cassette 12)
    - Howard Zinn and [Jon] Westling: Discussion on Equity, Mar 10, 1980; cuid17116; 448938 (Box 74, Cassette 13)
    - Howard Zinn: Visions of a New Society (Pendle Hill, PA) Part 1, May 6, 1980; cuid17117; 448939 (Box 86, Cd 1-2, Box 74, Cassette 14)
    - Howard Zinn: Visions of a New Society (Pendle Hill, PA) Part 2, May 6, 1980; cuid17118; 448940 (Box 86, Cd 1, Box 74, Cassette 15)
    - Howard Zinn: Grievance Meeting with Provost (Includes Joseph Meng, Eugene Green and Mary Mitchell), Nov 12, 1980; cuid17119; 448941 (Box 74, Cassette 16)
    - Howard Zinn: Interview, Great Atlantic Radio Conspiracy, 1980; cuid17120; 448942 (Box 74, Cassette 17)
    - Howard Zinn: Untitled Lecture (Scottsdale Community College, Phoenix, AZ), [1980]; cuid17121; 449640 (Box 74, Cassette 18)
    - Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on Plato - Apology and Crito, Feb 2, 1981; cuid17122; 449641 (Box 74, Cassette 19)
    - Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on Colonialism and the Distribution of Money, 1981; cuid17123; 449642 (Box 74, Cassette 20, Box Digitized Access Files, File TAM-542_ref1896)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      Duration: 16 min., Preservation Note: Due to deterioration of the source tape, only 9 minutes of side 1 and 6 minutes of side 2 were digitized.
    - Howard Zinn: Resistance to the Vietnam War (Central Michigan University, Mount Pleasant, MI) Part 1, Apr 28, 1982; cuid17124; 449643 (Box 74, Cassette 21)
    - Howard Zinn: Resistance to the Vietnam War (Central Michigan University, Mount Pleasant, MI) Part 2, Apr 28, 1982; cuid17125; 449644 (Box 74, Cassette 22)
    - Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on Race and Malcolm X, Oct 14, 1982; cuid17126; 449645 (Box 74, Cassette 23, Box 86, Box Digitized Access Files, File TAM-542_ref1899)
    - Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on Freedom of Speech Part 1, Oct 26, 1982; cuid17127; 449646 (Box 74, Cassette 24)
    - Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on Freedom of Speech Part 2, Oct 29, 1982; cuid17128; 449647 (Box 74, Cassette 25)
    - Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on Freedom of Information Part 1, [Nov] 1982; cuid17129; 449648 (Box 74, Cassette 26)
    - Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on Freedom of Information, Part 2, Nov 23, 1982; cuid17130; 449649 (Box 74, Cassette 27)
    - Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on Labor and the Law Parts 1 and 2, Nov 1982, Dec 2, 1982; cuid17131; 449650 (Box 74, Cassette 28)
    - Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on Race and Malcolm X, 1982; cuid17132; 449651; 1 sound disc (cd) (Box 74, Cassette 29, Box 86, Cd 1)
    - Howard Zinn: Is There an Ethics in Foreign Policy? (Assumption College, Worchester, MA) Part 1, Mar 16, 1983; cuid17133; 449652 (Box 74, Cassette 30)
    - Howard Zinn: Is There an Ethics in Foreign Policy? (Assumption College, Worchester, MA) Part 2, Mar 16, 1983; cuid17134; 449653 (Box 74, Cassette 31)
    - Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on the Constitution, Law and Justice, Sep 15, 1983; cuid17135; 449654 (Box 74, Cassette 32)
    - Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on Civil Disobedience, Sep 20, 1983; cuid17136; 449655 (Box 74, Cassette 33)
    - Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on the Black Struggle (with announcements at beginning of class), Oct 4, 1983; cuid17137; 449656 (Box 74, Cassette 34)
    - Howard Zinn: Class Lecture (Law and Justice), Oct 6, 1983; cuid17138; 449657 (Box 74, Cassette 35)
    - Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on Racial Inequality, Oct 11, 1983; cuid17139; 449658; 1 sound disc (cd) (Box 74, Cassette 36, Box 86, Cd 1)
    - Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on Malcolm X, Oct 13, 1983; cuid17140; 449659; 1 sound disc (cd) (Box 86, Cd 1, Box 74, Cassette 37)
    - Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on Free Speech, Oct 25, 1983; cuid17141; 449660 (Box 74, Cassette 38)
    - Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on War and Free Speech, Nov 1, 1983; cuid17142; 449661 (Box 74, Cassette 39)
    - Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on the U.S. Invasion of Grenada, Nov 3, 1983; cuid17143; 449662 (Box 74, Cassette 40)
    - Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on Vietnam, Nov 15, 1983; cuid17144; 449663 (Box 74, Cassette 41)
    - Howard Zinn: Class Lecture with [Steve Carpenter] - FBI and Thought Police, Nov 22, 1983; cuid17145; 449664 (Box 74, Cassette 42)
    - Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on Daniel Ellsberg and the Vietnam War, Nov 1983; cuid17146; 449665 (Box 74, Cassette 43)
    - Howard Zinn: Emma Goldman and Anarchism, Dec 8, 1983; cuid17147; 449666 (Box 74, Cassette 44)
    - Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on the Rosenberg Case, [Fall 1983]; cuid17148; 449667 (Box 74, Cassette 45)
    - Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on U.S. Involvement with Chile, Fall 1983; cuid17149; 449668 (Box 74, Cassette 46)
    - WHDH Mike Mill Show: Howard Zinn on U.S. Involvement in Central America and MA Referendum to End Funding for US Military Involvement in El Salvador, Honduras and Nicaragua, Oct 1984; cuid17150; 449669 (Box 74, Cassette 47)
    - Howard Zinn: Teach-In on American Intervention, Madison, WI, Apr 12, 1985; cuid17151; 449670 (Box 74, Cassette 48)
    - WORT Backporch Radio Broadcasting: A Public Affair - Howard Zinn, Teach-In on American Intervention (Madison, WI), Apr 12, 1985; cuid17152; 449671 (Box 74, Cassette 49)
    - Black Rose Lecture Series: Howard Zinn - "Marx and Bakunin: A Dialogue", Nov 15, 1985; cuid17153; 449672 (Box 74, Cassette 50)
    - Ron Kovic Speaking to Howard Zinn's Class on Law and Justice, Oct 30, 1986; cuid17154; 449673 (Box 74, Cassette 51)
    - Howard Zinn: "Second Thoughts on the First Amendment," (includes Q and A, Community Church of Boston, MA), Nov 16, 1986; cuid17155; 449674 (Box 74, Cassette 52)
    - WSLU: Evening Report - Howard Zinn, Interview on the Vietnam War, (Canton, NY), Mar 12, 1987; cuid17156; 449675 (Box 74, Cassette 53)
    - Howard Zinn: "Other American Dreams: Resistance in U.S. History," (Hampshire College, Amherst, MA), Sep 15, 1987; cuid17157; 449676 (Box 74, Cassette 54)
    - Sender Garlin: Lecture on the Life and Death of Joe Hill (University of Colorado, Boulder, CO), Jan 25, 1988; cuid17158; 449677 (Box 74, Cassette 55)
    - Howard Zinn: Last Class at Boston University (Boston, MA), Apr 1988; cuid17159; 449678 (Box 86, Cd 1, Box 74, Cassette 56)
    - WORT Backporch Radio Broadcasting: Second Opinion - Howard Zinn Interviewed by Erwin Knoll, Dec 1, 1988; cuid17160; 449679 (Box 74, Cassette 57)
    - Sender Garlin: Lecture on Mark Twain - Social Critic (University of Colorado, Boulder, CO), 1988; cuid17161; 449680 (Box 74, Cassette 58)
    - KGNU: Howard Zinn, Second Thoughts on the First Amendment (lecture, Boulder, CO) Tape 1, 1989; cuid17162; 449681 (Box 74, Cassette 59)
    - KGNU: Howard Zinn, Second Thoughts on the First Amendment (lecture, Boulder, CO) Tape 2, 1989; cuid17163; 449682 (Box 74, Cassette 60)
    - Lehigh-Pocono Committee of Concern (LEPOCO) 25th Anniversary Dinner: Howard Zinn - Surprises in History (Bethlehem, PA), Mar 9, 1990; cuid17164; 449683 (Box 74, Cassette 61)
    - Emma: A Play in Two Acts about Emma Goldman, American Anarchist (No 1) by Howard Zinn, Performed in Tokyo (Japanese Version), May 24, 1990; cuid17165; 449684 (Box 74, Cassette 62)
    - Emma: A Play in Two Acts about Emma Goldman, American Anarchist (No 2) by Howard Zinn, Performed in Tokyo (Japanese Version), May 24, 1990; cuid17166; 449685 (Box 74, Cassette 63)
    - KPFK: Continent to Continent - Howard Zinn, "Columbus: Villain Portrayed as Hero," Also Includes Odessa Ramirez and Phillip Tajitsu Nash (Los Angeles, CA), Oct 3, 1990; cuid17167; 449686 (Box 74, Cassette 64)
    - WMFO: Howard Zinn - Just and Unjust Wars, Mar 8, 1991; cuid17168; 449687 (Box 74, Cassette 65)
    - WOMR: Two Good Arms - Howard Zinn on the Julius and Ethel Rosenberg Trial, Jun 1991; cuid17169; 449688 (Box 74, Cassette 66)
    - WOMR: Two Good Arms - Howard Zinn on the Julius and Ethel Rosenberg Trial/ Sacco and Vanzetti Commemoration (Aug 23, 1990)/ May Day (1991) Presentation/ Report on Jesse Helm's Attack on the National Endowment for the Arts (Provincetown, MA), Jun 1991/ Aug 23, 1990/ 1991/ undated; cuid17170; 449689 (Box 74, Cassette 67)
    - Monadnock Summer Lyceum: Howard Zinn - "A Second Look at the First Amendment: Free Speech" (Petersborough Unitarian Church, Peterborough, NH), Jul 7, 1991; cuid17171; 449690 (Box 74, Cassette 68)
    - New Hampshire Public Radio: Howard Zinn - Interview Tape 1, Jul 11, 1991; cuid17172; 449691 (Box 74, Cassette 69)
    - New Hampshire Public Radio: Howard Zinn - Interview Tape 2, Jul 11, 1991; cuid17173; 449692 (Box 74, Cassette 70)
    - Howard Zinn: "Columbus Legacy: 1492-1992" (Wellfleet Public Library, Wellfleet, MA), Aug 29, 1991; cuid17174; 449693 (Box 74, Cassette 71)
    - Howard Zinn: "Just and Unjust Wars" (Wellfleet Public Library, Wellfleet, MA), Sep 3, 1991; cuid17175; 449694 (Box 74, Cassette 72)
    - WOMR: Howard Zinn - "Second Thoughts on the First Amendment" (Recorded Sep 7, 1991, Broadcast Dec 13, 1991 and Dec 20, 1991, Wellfleet, MA), cuid17176; 449695 (Box 74, Cassette 73)
    - Gray Panthers Meeting: Howard Zinn, Economic Bill of Rights (Cambridge, MA), Oct 18, 1991; cuid17177; 449696 (Box 74, Cassette 74)
    - Radio Free Maine: Howard Zinn - Speaking Out on the CIA (Franklin Pierce College, NH), Oct 28, 1991; cuid17178; 449697 (Box 74, Cassette 75)
    - WBAI: Howard Zinn - Multiculturalism in Education, Nov 30, 1991; cuid17179; 449698 (Box 74, Cassette 76)
    - Radio Free Maine / Massachusetts Civil Liberties Union: "Born in the USA- 200 Years Old Today, Bill of Rights Celebration" (Includes Barry Crimmins, Ira Glasser, Molly Ivins, Mel King, Howard Zinn and Ted O'Brien, Old South Meeting House, Boston, MA) Part 1, Dec 15, 1991; cuid17180; 449699 (Box 74, Cassette 77)
    - Radio Free Maine / Massachusetts Civil Liberties Union: "Born in the USA- 200 Years Old Today, Bill of Rights Celebration" (Includes Barry Crimmins, Ira Glasser, Molly Ivins, Mel King, Howard Zinn and Ted O'Brien, Old South Meeting House, Boston, MA) Part 2, Dec 15, 1991; cuid17181; 449700 (Box 74, Cassette 78)
    - WOMR: Talking Together, Holiday Greetings, Dec 27, 1991; cuid17182; 449701 (Box 74, Cassette 79)
    - Radio Free Maine: Howard Zinn - Aftermath of Persian Gulf War; Just and Unjust Wars (Boston College, MA), Feb 5, 1992; cuid17183; 449702 (Box 74, Cassette 80)
    - WOMR: Talking Together - Howard Zinn on Presidents, the Presidency and the Electorate, Feb 21, 1992; cuid17184; 449703 (Box 74, Cassette 81)
    - Sender Garlin: Lecture on Jack London - "Romantic Revolutionary", Apr 14, 1992; cuid17185; 449704 (Box 74, Cassette 82)
    - Howard Zinn: A People's History of the United States, Read by Geri Librandi - Chapter 1 "Columbus, the Indians and Human Progress", 1992; cuid17186; 449705 (Box 74, Cassette 83)
    - Howard Zinn: A People's History of the United States, Read by Geri Librandi - Chapter 2 "Drawing the Color Line", Chapter 4, "Tyranny is Tyranny", 1992; cuid17187; 449706 (Box 74, Cassette 84)
    - Howard Zinn: A People's History of the United States, Read by Geri Librandi - Chapter 3 "Persons of Mean and Vile Condition", 1992; cuid17188; 449707 (Box 74, Cassette 85)
    - Howard Zinn: A People's History of the United States, Read by Geri Librandi - Chapter 5 "A Kind Revolution", 1992; cuid17189; 449708 (Box 74, Cassette 86)
    - Howard Zinn: A People's History of the United States, Read by Geri Librandi - Chapter 6 "The Intimately Oppressed", 1992; cuid17190; 449709 (Box 74, Cassette 87)
    - Howard Zinn: A People's History of the United States, Read by Geri Librandi - Chapter 7 "As Long as Grass Grows or Water Runs", 1992; cuid17191; 449710 (Box 74, Cassette 88)
    - Howard Zinn: A People's History of the United States, Read by Geri Librandi - Chapter 8 "We Take Nothing By Conquest, Thank God", 1992; cuid17192; 449711 (Box 74, Cassette 89)
    - Howard Zinn: A People's History of the United States, Read by Geri Librandi - Chapter 9 "Slavery Without Submission, Emancipation Without Freedom", 1992; cuid17193; 449712 (Box 74, Cassette 90)
    - Howard Zinn: A People's History of the United States, Read by Geri Librandi - Chapter 9 continued, Chapter 10 "The Other Civil War", 1992; cuid17194; 449713 (Box 74, Cassette 91)
    - Howard Zinn: A People's History of the United States, Read by Geri Librandi - Chapter 10 continued, 1992; cuid17195; 449714 (Box 74, Cassette 92)
    - Howard Zinn: A People's History of the United States, Read by Geri Librandi - Chapter 11 "Robber Barons and Rebels", 1992; cuid17196; 449715 (Box 74, Cassette 93)
    - Howard Zinn: A People's History of the United States, Read by Geri Librandi - Chapter 11 continued, 1992; cuid17197; 449716 (Box 74, Cassette 94)
    - Howard Zinn: "Columbus Legacy: 1492-1992" (California Polytechnic, CA), cuid17198; 449717 (Box 74, Cassette 95)
    - Radio Free Maine: Howard Zinn, "Emma Goldman: Dangerous Woman" (Radcliffe College, Cambridge, MA), Feb 24, 1993; cuid17199; 449718 (Box 74, Cassette 96)
    - Radio Free Maine: Howard Zinn, "Emma Goldman: Dangerous Woman" (Radcliffe College, Cambridge, MA), Feb 24, 1993; cuid17200; 449719 (Box 74, Cassette 96 dup)
    - Radio Free Maine: Howard Zinn - "The New Patriotism; War, Peace and Me" (Newbury College, Brookline, MA), Apr 20, 1993; cuid17201; 449720 (Box 74, Cassette 97)
    - Howard Zinn: "Lecture on History, Politics and Objectivity" (Harvey Goldberg Lecture Series, University of Wisconsin, Madison, WI) Tape 1, [Sep 1993]; cuid17202; 449721 (Box 74, Cassette 98, Box Digitized Access Files, File TAM-542_ref1975)
      Duration: 65 min.
    - Howard Zinn: "Lecture on History, Politics and Objectivity" (Harvey Goldberg Lecture Series, University of Wisconsin, Madison, WI) Tape 2, [Sep 1993]; cuid17203; 449722 (Box 74, Cassette 99, Box Digitized Access Files, File TAM-542_ref1976)
      Duration: 29 min.
    - Radio Free Maine: Howard Zinn - "The Use and Abuse of History" (University of New Hampshire, Durham, NH), Mar 9, 1994; cuid17204; 449723 (Box 74, Cassette 100, Box Digitized Access Files, File TAM-542_ref1977)
      Duration: 77 min.
    - Radio Free Maine: Howard Zinn - "The Use and Abuse of History" (University of New Hampshire, Durham, NH), Mar 9, 1994; cuid17205; 449724 (Box 74, Cassette 100 dup)
    - Radio Free Maine: Howard Zinn - "The Clinton Administration: Its Historical Perspective" (University of Maine, Farmington, ME), Mar 29, 1994; cuid17206; 449725 (Box 74, Cassette 101, Box Digitized Access Files, File TAM-542_ref1979)
      Duration: 92 min.
    - Radio Free Maine: Talking Together Lecture: Howard Zinn, "Can History Prepare Us for the Twenty-First Century?" (Wellfleet Public Library, Wellfleet, MA), Aug 11, 1994; cuid17207; 449726 (Box 74, Cassette 102, Box Digitized Access Files, File TAM-542_ref1980)
      Duration: 90 min.
    - Talking Together: Howard Zinn - "Can History Prepare Us for the Twenty-First Century?" (Wellfleet Public Library, Wellfleet, MA), Aug 11, 1994; cuid17208; 449727 (Box 74, Cassette 103, Box Digitized Access Files, File TAM-542_ref1981)
      Duration: 94 min.
    - Radio Free Maine: Howard Zinn - "The Use and Abuse of History" (St Michael's College, Winooski, VT), Oct 4, 1994; cuid17209; 449728 (Box 74, Cassette 104, Box Digitized Access Files, File TAM-542_ref1982)
      Duration: 93 min.
    - WPR: Ideas Network - Howard Zinn Interviewed by Jean Feraca on You Can't Be Neutral on a Moving Train (Madison, WI), Nov 29, 1994; cuid17210; 449729 (Box 74, Cassette 105, Box Digitized Access Files, File TAM-542_ref1983)
      Duration: 53 min.
    - Howard Zinn: Myth and Reality in the Teaching of American History (Chautauqua Institution, Chautauqua, NY), 1994; cuid17211; 449730 (Box 74, Cassette 106, Box Digitized Access Files, File TAM-542_ref1984)
      Duration: 76 min.
    - Second Opinion / The Progressive: Howard Zinn, Interviewed by Matthew Rothschild on You Can't Be Neutral on a Moving Train (also includes interview with Marita Golden), Feb 10, 1995/Feb 17, 1995; cuid17212; 449731 (Box 74, Cassette 107, Box Digitized Access Files, File TAM-542_ref1985)
      Duration: 80 min.
    - WOMR: Talking Together - Howard Zinn Interviewed by Matthew Rothschild on You Can't Be Neutral on a Moving Train (Broadcast May 4, 1995), Feb 10, 1995; cuid17213; 449732 (Box 74, Cassette 108, Box Digitized Access Files, File TAM-542_ref1986)
      Duration: 62 min.
    - Radio Free Maine: Howard Zinn, You Can't Be Neutral on a Moving Train - Education and Activism, Feb 13, 1995; cuid17214; 449733 (Box 74, Cassette 109, Box Digitized Access Files, File TAM-542_ref1987)
    - David Barsamian: "Corporate Power, Profits Before People" (Santa Cruz, CA), Oct 13, 1995; cuid17215; 449734 (Box 74, Cassette 110, Box Digitized Access Files, File TAM-542_ref1988)
      Duration: 74 min.
    - Howard Zinn: A People's History of the United States (Portland, OR), Nov 20, 1995; cuid17216; 449735 (Box 74, Cassette 111, Box Digitized Access Files, File TAM-542_ref1989)
      Duration: 60 min.
    - City Arts of San Francisco: Alice Walker and Howard Zinn in Discussion on Writing and Activism, Hosted by Maya Angelou (San Francisco, CA), [1995]; cuid17217; 449736 (Box 74, Cassette 112)
    - Women's Foundation of California / City Arts: Alice Walker in Discussion with Howard Zinn, Jan 17, 1996; cuid17218; 449737 (Box 74, Cassette 113)
    - WBAI: Howard Zinn - Lecture on History, Education and Objectivity (Fullerton College, Fullerton, CA) / Chris Whent Radio Show, Oct 12, 1996/Jun 6, 1992; cuid17219; 449738 (Box 74, Cassette 114)
    - Alice Walker: My Life as My Self, 1996; cuid17220; 449739 (Box 74, Cassette 115)
    - KPFA: Anything We Love Can Be Saved - Mothers' Day Eve with Alice Walker (King Middle School, Berkeley, CA), May 10, 1997; cuid17221; 449740 (Box 74, Cassette 116)
    - WORT: A Public Affair - Howard Zinn Interviewed by James Carrott on You Can't Be Neutral on a Moving Train, Jul 15, 1997; cuid17222; 449741 (Box 74, Cassette 117)
    - KPFA: Mario Savio Memorial Lecture - Howard Zinn "The Possibility of Hope: Our Legacy from the Sixties," University of California, Berkeley, CA, Nov 13, 1997; cuid17223; 449742 (Box 74, Cassette 118)
    - WORT: A Public Affair - Howard Zinn (Interview on the Uses of History), Nov 18, 1997; cuid17224; 449743 (Box 74, Cassette 119)
    - Howard Zinn: Lecture on the Uses of History (Wisconsin Historical Society, Madison, WI), Nov 18, 1997; cuid17225; 449744 (Box 74, Cassette 120)
    - Howard Zinn: Lecture on History, Politics and Objectivity (Portland, OR), Jan 22, 1998; cuid17226; 449745 (Box 74, Cassette 121)
    - Howard Zinn: One Hundred Years of U.S. Imperialism (Old Cambridge Baptist Church, Cambridge, MA), Jun 30, 1998; cuid17227; 449746 (Box 74, Cassette 122)
    - Alternative Radio: Eqbal Ahmad - "Terrorism: Theirs and Ours" (Boulder, CO), Oct 12, 1998; cuid17228; 449747 (Box 74, Cassette 123)
    - Alternative Radio: Eqbal Ahmad - Boulder Interviews (Boulder, CO), Oct 12, 1998-Oct 13, 1998; cuid17229; 449748 (Box 74, Cassette 124)
    - People's Tribune Radio: Howard Zinn, A Working Class Citizen's Economic Bill of Rights, Also Includes Nelson Peery, Oct 1998; cuid17230; 449749 (Box 74, Cassette 125)
    - Howard Zinn: Bringing Democracy Alive (University of Colorado, Denver, CO) Tape 1, 1998; cuid17231; 449750 (Box 74, Cassette 126)
    - Howard Zinn: Bringing Democracy Alive (University of Colorado, Denver, CO) Tape 2, 1998; cuid17232; 449751 (Box 74, Cassette 127)
    - WNYC: New York and Company - Howard Zinn (Interview), Jan 15, 1999; cuid17233; 449752 (Box 74, Cassette 128)
    - WUSB: Critique - Howard Zinn (Interview, Stony Brook, NY), [Feb 1, 1999]; cuid17234; 449753 (Box 74, Cassette 129)
    - Alternative Radio: Howard Zinn - War and Democracy (Chestnut Hill, MA), Nov 11, 1999; cuid17235; 449754 (Box 74, Cassette 130)
    - Common Courage Press: "Zinn at the Heart of History: An Interview with Howard Zinn by Greg Bates on Objectivity and Optimism", 1999; cuid17236; 449755 (Box 74, Cassette 131)
    - WUSB: Howard Zinn (Interview, Stony Brook, NY), Jan 29, 2000; cuid17237; 449756 (Box 74, Cassette 132)
    - WNYC: New York and Company - Interviews on Howard Zinn on History and Howard Zinn on War, [2000]; cuid17238; 449757 (Box 74, Cassette 133)
    - Alternative Radio: Arundhati Roy - "A Writer's Place in Politics" (Amherst, MA), Feb 15, 2001; cuid17239; 449758 (Box 74, Cassette 134)
    - Alternative Radio: Howard Zinn - "Artists in a Time of War" (Massachusetts College of Art, Boston, MA), Oct 10, 2001; cuid17240; 449759 (Box 74, Cassette 135)
    - Alternative Radio: Howard Zinn - "Artists in a Time of War" (Massachusetts College of Art, Boston, MA), Oct 10, 2001; cuid17241; 449760 (Box 74, Cassette 135 dup)
    - WMBR: Anti-War Rally in Boston / Nov 2001 News (Democracy Rising Tour and Day of Mourning), Oct 12, 2001/Nov 2001; cuid17242; 449761 (Box 74, Cassette 136)
    - WAMU: Howard Zinn Interviewed by Diane Rehm on Terrorism and War, the Anti-War Movement and Alternatives to War (American University, Washington, DC), Jul 11, 2002; cuid17243; 449762 (Box 74, Cassette 137)